<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
    <xt:extension id="com.oxygenxml.image.markup">
        <xt:location href="image-markup-plugin-1.0.0-SNAPSHOT-plugin.jar"/>
        <xt:version>1.0.0</xt:version>
        <xt:oxy_version>14.0+</xt:oxy_version>
        <xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
        <xt:author>"TEI Facsimile Plugin" Open Source Project</xt:author>
        <xt:name>TEI Facsimile Plugin</xt:name>
        <xt:description xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">A plugin that helps marking zones for a digital facsimile. 
            After installation, if you want to quickly test it, you can just click <b>Image Markup Sample</b> on the toolbar.
            This will automatically perform the following steps on some sample files. If you want to use your own files, you must:
            <ol>
                <li>Go to <i>Window->Show View</i> and click on <b>Image-Markup</b></li>
                <li>Open a TEI document that contains facsimile information.</li>
                <li>In the newly open editor, select an image name (for example <i>Bovelles-49r.png</i>) and press <b>Open Selected</b> in the <b>Image-Markup</b> view.</li>
            </ol>
            
            <p><b>Supported features:</b></p>
            <ul>
                <li>If you place yourself in a <i>zone</i> element inside the document, that element will be painted
                    with a different color.</li>
                <li>If you right click on a zone in image view, you can either delete it (and will
                    reflect in the editor) or copy it and then paste it in the document.</li>
                <li>You can use the mouse to draw a new rectangle over the image. Then right click
                    and copy its coordinates to paste them in the editor.</li>
                <li>You can resize an existing rectangle from one of its corners.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>Known limitations (which can be addressed with some Java skills and free time):</p>
            <ul>
                <li>All <i>zone</i> elements are being rendered. Ideally only the <i>zone</i>
                    elements from the <i>surface</i> element with the loaded image should be
                    rendered.</li>
                <li>New zone elements that are manually inserted in the document will not be
                    rendered automatically. You'll have to reload the image.</li>
            </ul>
            </xt:description>
        <xt:license>
<![CDATA[
Copyright 2013 Syncro Soft SRL, Romania. All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are
permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of
conditions and the following disclaimer.

2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list
of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials
provided with the distribution.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY Syncro Soft SRL ''AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL Syncro Soft SRL OR
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

THIRD-PARTY LIBRARIES AND RESOURCES
Third party libraries and resources redistributed in this package are subject to their 
respective licenses.

]]></xt:license>
    </xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>
